Guide to the Time Inc. Corporate Editorial Records 1948-1983, undated (bulk 1959-1979) MS 3009-RG 6.I MS 3009-RG 6TEST
© 2011 New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Editor-in-Chief: Subseries I.A. Hedley Donovan Files, 1948-1983, undated (bulk 1959-1979); 56.0 Linear feet; (56 boxes)
  - Subsubseries I.A.3. Audiovisual, 1966-1977, undated; 2.0 Linear feet; (2 boxes)
    - Undated (Offsite-box 785, Folder 10)
      1 audiocassette (Scotch C-60): analog, 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. On container label: "Grunwald. To be returned to Anne Rhoads in Alex Burnham's office - Room 2339."
      1 audiocassette (Norelco C-60): analog, 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. On container label: "Revised for air - 3/24. 'On Target Every Day with 4 1/2 million readers.' Tony Burton. Ella Elvin [?]. Didi Olive [?]. Phil Rizenburgh [?]. Burt Shanus [?]." Accompanying note states these are a sample of Daily News reporters talking about their work.
    - Undated (Offsite-box 785, Folder 11)
      2 audiotape reels, analog, 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. On container label: "1st tape."
    - Undated (Offsite-box 785, Folder 12)
      1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. On container label: "2nd tape."
    - Undated (Offsite-box 785, Folder 13)
      1 audiocassette: analog, 1 7/8 ips; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. On label side 1: "Program #8 'The Course of Human Events.' Part 1 28:09 OQ:SQI Thank you all." On label side 2: "Program #8 'The Course of Human Events.' Audience. Part 2 OQ: For group W. 24:19."
    - Undated (Box 785, Folder 14)
      1 audiotape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 1/4 in. tape. On container label: "3 3/4 I.P.S. 'Caduceus [?] Society Banquet.' Side # I. Introduction by Frederic T. Kirkham Jr., MD. 'Speaker' Hedley Donovan Editor in chief - Time Inc. 'Relationships of USA & Russia'."
- Series I. Editor-in-Chief: Subseries I.B. Henry Anatole Grunwald Files, 1944-1998 (bulk 1968-1987); 74.0 Linear feet; (74 boxes)
  Henry Anatole Grunwald began his career at Time Inc. in 1944 as a copy boy and worked to the top editorial position of Editor-in-Chief.
  Grunwald emigrated to the United States from Austria in 1940 at the age of 17. After graduating from New York University in 1944, he began his first job at Time Inc. Grunwald held positions as a foreign correspondent from 1945 to 1951, Time Senior Editor from 1951 to 1966, Time Assistant Managing Editor from 1966 to 1968, Time Managing Editor from 1968 to 1977, Corporate Editor from 1977 to 1979, and finally was appointed as Editor-in-Chief in 1979 by his predecessor Hedley Donovan. He also served on Time Inc.'s board.
  During his tenure as Editor-in-Chief, Grunwald appointed the first woman managing editor of a major Time Inc. magazine when Patricia Ryan took over People in 1982.
  After retiring from Time Inc. President Ronald Reagan named him U.S. ambassador to Austria. Beginning in 1997, Grunwald published two memoirs, One Man's America, recounting his experiences as a Jewish refugee from Nazi-controlled Europe and success in his adopted country, and Twilight: Losing Sight, Gaining Insight about his degenerative loss of eyesight. In 2003, he published the novel A Saint, More or Less.
  Schudel, Matt. "Henry Grunwald, Managing Editor of Time Magazine, Dies." The Washington Post. February 27, 2005. Accessed August 29, 2017. http://www.washingtonpost.com/wp-dyn/articles/A56472-2005Feb26.html
  The Henry Anatole Grunwald Files primarily are during his tenures as Time Managing Editor, Editorial Director, and Editor-in-Chief with some records from earlier in his career. Based on the accompanying archives transfer forms, all of Grunwald's files were transferred by his office while he was Editor-in-Chief. Therefore the records are not separated based on office and title, but kpet in the series designated by his office on the transfer forms. Records include his internal and external correspondence, departmental files, files on Newstours he attended, speeches, and travel records.
  Organized into eight subsubseries:
  Subsubseries I.B.1. General Correspondence
  Subsubseries I.B.2. Interoffice Correspondence
  Subsubseries I.B.3. Departmental Files
  Subsubseries I.B.4. Newstours
  Subsubseries I.B.5. Photographs
  Subsubseries I.B.6. Speeches
  Subsubseries I.B.7. Trips
  Subsubseries I.A.8. Archives Transfer Forms
  - Subsubseries I.B.1. General Correspondence, 1944-1987; 13.0 Linear feet; (13 boxes)
    General Correspondence is primarily correspondence to and from people outside of the Time Inc. although "General: A-Z" contains a mix of internal and external correspondents and looks like Grunwald’s office chron files. "General: Letters" are solely external correspondents.
    External correspondents include former Time Inc. employees such as James Shepley and Hedley Donovan; non-Time Inc. staff members of the board (Sol M. Linowitz and Thomas J. Watson, Jr.); Time subscribers; freelance journalists; editors from other magazines such as Helen Gurley Brown (Cosmopolitan) and Malcom Forbes; authors; book publishers; current and former government officials such as members of Congress (Patrick Moynihan), state governors, and United States ambassadors, including former Time Inc. employee Herman Nickel, and other Department of State officials; heads of companies such as Armand Hammer (Occidental Petroleum), Katharine Graham (The Washington Post Company), Cornell Capa (International Center for Photography), and John Diebold (The Diebold Group); presidents and professors of universities; and other notable people. There is correspondence of a mixed social and official nature with notable figures who also seem to be personal friends or acquaintances such as Ben Netanyahu, Richard Nixon, Sol Linowitz, Henry Kissinger, and Ronald and Nancy Reagan.
    Records includes comments and complaints on articles from readers or the subjects of the articles such as the Cherokee Nation (1968), the Mayor of San Diego (1969); and Ralph Nadar (1976); internal memoranda regarding these comments or complaints; offers for and discussion of writing assignments; invitations to be a guest speaker; travel arrangements; notifications of notable visitors to Time Inc.; applications to associations such as Chaos Club and Century Club; discussion of recently attended events; and general social correspondence.
    Items of interest include two early letters from Grunwald to Content Peckham during his first job as a copy boy (1944-1952); a thank you letter from Judge Sirica on being named Man of the Year (1974); a very angry letter from Kurt Vonnegut regarding a People article (1979); a letter from Fidel Castro Ruz (1981); complaints from Accuracy in Media in its early years; slide photographs from a 1977 Irving Lazar party; years-long correspondence with Vladimir Nabokov; an invitation from Diane von Furstenburg for Gloria Steinem's 50th birthday (1984); and several letters between him and the Reagans including handwritten notes from Nancy.
    In 2004, shortly before Grunwald's death, his files were reviewed by a family representative and parts were removed to return to his family. In most instances, photocopies take their place. In some instances, there are notes from Time Inc. librarian C. Weil indicating what was removed. Removals include "items of personal nature, family, real estate on Vineyard."
    Organized chronologically by year, and alphabetically within each year based on the original arrangement.
    - 1944-1952 (Offsite-box 762, Folder 11-12)
    - 1951-1968 (Offsite-box 762, Folder 13)
    - 1963-1964 (Offsite-box 762, Folder 14-22)
    - 1963-1964 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1965-1967 (Offsite-box 762, 987)
    - 1968-1969 (Offsite-box 987-988)
    - 1970-1972 (Offsite-box 988-989)
    - 1971-1972 (Offsite-box 989)
      The "I" folder contains an original watercolor by Jean Michel Folon loaned by Grunwald to another publication.
    - 1973: A-H (Offsite-box 989)
    - 1973: J-Z (Offsite-box 990)
    - 1974: A-J (Offsite-box 990)
    - 1974: K-Z (Offsite-box 991)
    - 1974: K-Z [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1975: A-G (Offsite-box 991)
    - 1975: H-Z (Offsite-box 992)
    - 1975: H-Z [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1976: Letters: A-H (Offsite-box 992-993)
    - 1976: Letters: I-Z (Offsite-box 993)
    - 1977: Letters: A-Z (Offsite-box 993)
    - 1978: Letters: A-E (Offsite-box 993)
    - 1978: Letters: F-M (Offsite-box 993-994)
    - 1978: Letters: N-Z (Offsite-box 994)
    - 1979: Letters: A-Z (Offsite-box 994)
    - 1981: Letters: A-D (Offsite-box 994-995)
    - 1981: Letters: A-D [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1981: Letters: E-Z (Offsite-box 995)
    - 1982: Letters: A-D (Offsite-box 995)
    - 1982: Letters: E-K (Offsite-box 995-996)
      1 audiocassette: analog; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. On label: "12-1-82. Tape I. Recorded at THE NEW SCHOOL, 66 West 12th Street, N.Y. 10011."
      1 audiocassette: analog; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. On label: "12/1/82. Tape II. Recorded at THE NEW SCHOOL, 66 West 12th Street, N.Y. 10011."
    - 1982: Letters: L-Z (Offsite-box 996)
    - 1983: Letters: A-Z (Offsite-box 996)
    - 1984: Letters: A-Z (Offsite-box 997)
    - 1984: Letters: A-Z [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1985: Letters: A-Z (Offsite-box 997)
    - 1986: Letters: A-Z (Offsite-box 998)
    - 1986: Letters: A-Z [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1987: A-M (Offsite-box 998)
    - 1987: A-M [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1987: N-Z (Offsite-box 999)
    - 1987: Telephone Message Books (Offsite-box 999)
  - Subsubseries I.B.2. Interoffice Correspondence, 1972-1987; 20.0 Linear feet; (20 boxes)
    Interoffice Correspondence is primarily correspondence and memoranda to and from Time Inc. staff regarding work matters. Frequent correspondents have individual folders and the rest of the correspondence is in memo files. The correspondents are mainly managing editors and publishers of the major magazines, members of the Magazine Development Department, and heads of corporate offices. Folders with an individual’s name may contain correspondence from others forwarded by the named person.
    Frequent interoffice correspondents and titles held relevant to these records include:
    Louis Banks: Editorial Director, board member, and consultant after retirement; Don Barr: Time General Manager, Sports Illustrated Associate Publisher and Advertising Sales Director
    Reginald Brack: Chief Executive Officer of Time Inc.'s magazine group
    Ruth Brine: Time researcher and Senior Editor
    Ray Cave: Sports Illustrated Assistant Managing Editor, Time Managing Editor, Corporate Editor and Editorial Director
    George Constable: Time-Life Books Managing Editor
    Ralph Davidson: Time Publisher, assistant to Time Inc. president James Shepley, and Chairman of the Board
    Hedley Donovan: Editor-in-Chief before Grunwald and consultant after 1979 retirement
    Dick Duncan: Time-Life News Service reporter then Chief of Correspondents
    Murray Gart: Time Assistant Managing Editor, Time-Life News Service Chief of Correspondents, and the final Washington Star Editor
    Leah Gordon: Time Letters Editor, Chief of Research, and Time Administrative Editor
    Ralph Graves: Editorial Director and consultant after 1983 retirement
    Edward Jamieson: Time Assistant Managing Editor then Executive Editor
    Leon Jaroff: Discover Managing Editor
    Jeanne Kerr: Vice President of Corporate Contributions
    Ron Kriss: Time Executive Editor
    Phil Kunhardt: Life Managing Editor and a member of Magazine Development
    Marshall Loeb: Time Senior Editor and Economics Editor, Money Managing Editor, and Magazine Development Managing Editor
    Joan Manley: Board member and Group Vice President of Books
    Carolyn McCandless: Assistant Secretary and Vice President and Director of Employee Benefits
    Jason McManus: Time Managing Editor and successor as Editor-in-Chief to Grunwald
    J. Richard Munro: Vice President then Executive Vice President for television and films, and President and Chief Executive Officer
    Nicholas J. Nicholas: Chief Financial Officer, Executive Vice President for video operations, board member, and President and co-Chief Executive
    Curt Prendergast: Time foreign correspondent and co-author of The World of Time Inc.: Volume Three, 1961-1980
    Gil Rogin: Managing Editor of Discover and Corporate Editor
    Bill Rukeyser: founding Money Managing Editor and Fortune Managing Editor
    Patricia Ryan: first woman Managing Editor of any major Time Inc. publication as People Managing Editor
    Robert Steed: Personnel Office Director
    Richard Stolley: Managing Editor of People, Life, Picture Week, and Magazine Development
    Kelso Sutton: Sports Illustrated Publisher, Vice President then Executive Vice President of the Magazine Group, President of the Books Division, and board member
    Donald Wilson: Vice President of Corporate Public Affairs.
    Topics discussed include frequent comparisons and tracking of Newsweek, Time’s major competitor; ideas Grunwald likes seen in other publications; comments on articles and projects; history of the Time Index in 1975; cost control considerations in 1975; extensive comments on writing style and word use; starting a women's magazine in 1976 and 1977; reviving Life in 1977; reorganizing Time Inc. in 1977; donating the Time cover art collection which ultimately went to the National Portrait Gallery in 1978; staff appointments including their history with Time Inc.; magazine development and proposals; board elections and new corporate staff, earnings reports; redesign of Fortune; Time Inc.'s affirmative action attempts; evaluations of Editorial departments (usually by Frank Lalli); notes from Phil Kunhardt on Life history; meeting agenda and transcripts. Staff Memos are on topics such as writing style points, announcements, masthead changes, and development of new staff positions.
    Organized chronologically by year, and alphabetically by last name within each year with additional memo and other files at the end of each year based on the original arrangement.
    - 1972: Banks, Louis (Offsite-box 999, Folder 14)
    - 1972: Barr, Don (Offsite-box 999, Folder 15)
    - 1972: Brine, Ruth (Offsite-box 999, Folder 16)
    - 1972: Davidson, Ralph and Hank Luce (Offsite-box 999, Folder 17)
    - 1972: Donovan, Hedley (Offsite-box 999, Folder 18)
    - 1972: Gart, Murray (Offsite-box 999, Folder 19)
    - 1972: Jamieson, Edward (Offsite-box 999, Folder 20)
    - 1972: Loeb, Marshall [empty] (Offsite-box 999, Folder 21)
    - 1972: Vega, Marylois (Offsite-box 999, Folder 22)
    - 1972: Werner, Lucy (Offsite-box 999, Folder 23)
    - 1972: Memos to/from Correspondents (Domestic) (Offsite-box 999, Folder 24)
    - 1972: Memos to/from Correspondents (Foreign) (Offsite-box 999, Folder 25)
    - 1972: Memos to Staff (Offsite-box 999, Folder 26)
    - 1973: Barr, Don (Offsite-box 999, Folder 27)
    - 1973: Cate, Ben (Offsite-box 999, Folder 28)
    - 1973: Clive, Bob (Offsite-box 999, Folder 29)
    - 1973: Davidson, Ralph (Offsite-box 999, Folder 30-31)
    - 1973: Donovan, Hedley (Offsite-box 1000, Folder 1-2)
    - 1973: Gart, Murray (Offsite-box 1000, Folder 3-4)
    - 1973: Gordon, Leah (Offsite-box 1000, Folder 5)
    - 1973: Graves, Ralph (Offsite-box 1000, Folder 6)
    - 1973: Jamieson, Edward (Offsite-box 1000, Folder 7)
    - 1973: McConathy, Dale (Offsite-box 1000, Folder 8)
    - 1973: Sidey, Hugh (Offsite-box 1000, Folder 9)
    - 1973: Vega, Marylois (Offsite-box 1000, Folder 10)
    - 1973: Memos (Offsite-box 1000, Folder 11)
    - 1973: Memos [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1973: Staff Memos (Offsite-box 1000, Folder 12)
    - 1974: Barr, Don (Offsite-box 1000, Folder 13)
    - 1974: Birnbaum, Jesse (Offsite-box 1000, Folder 14)
    - 1974: Cate, Ben (Offsite-box 1000, Folder 15)
    - 1974: Davidson, Ralph (Offsite-box 1000, Folder 16-17)
    - 1974: Donovan, Hedley (Offsite-box 1000, Folder 18-19)
    - 1974: Gart, Murray (Offsite-box 1000, Folder 20-21)
    - 1974: Jackson, Ed (Offsite-box 1000, Folder 22)
    - 1974: Jamieson, Edward (Offsite-box 1000, Folder 23)
    - 1974: Vega, Marylois (Offsite-box 1000, Folder 24)
    - 1974: Memos (Offsite-box 1000-1001)
    - 1974: Staff Memos (Offsite-box 1001, Folder 3)
    - 1974: Wires: Domestic (Offsite-box 1001, Folder 4)
    - 1975: Barr, Don (Offsite-box 1001, Folder 5)
    - 1975: Cave, Ray (Offsite-box 1001, Folder 6)
    - 1975: Davidson, Ralph (Offsite-box 1001, Folder 7)
    - 1975: Donovan, Hedley (Offsite-box 1001, Folder 8-9)
    - 1975: Duncan, Dick (Offsite-box 1001, Folder 10)
    - 1975: Gart, Murray (Offsite-box 1001, Folder 11-12)
    - 1975: Graves, Ralph (Offsite-box 1001, Folder 13)
    - 1975: Jackson, Ed (Offsite-box 1001, Folder 14)
    - 1975: Jamieson, Edward (Offsite-box 1001, Folder 15)
    - 1975: Vega, Marylois (Offsite-box 1001, Folder 16)
    - 1975: Vega, Marylois [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1975: Staff Memos (Offsite-box 1001, Folder 17)
    - 1975: Memos: January-December (Offsite-box 1001, Folder 18-29)
    - 1975: Bad English Memo (Offsite-box 1001, Folder 30)
    - 1976: Barr, Don (Offsite-box 1001, Folder 31)
    - 1976: Birnbaum, Jesse (Offsite-box 1001, Folder 32)
    - 1976: Cave, Ray (Offsite-box 1001, Folder 33)
    - 1976: Davidson, Ralph (Offsite-box 1001, Folder 34)
    - 1976: Donovan, Hedley (Offsite-box 1001, Folder 35-37)
    - 1976: Duncan, Dick (Offsite-box 1002, Folder 1)
    - 1976: Elson, John (Offsite-box 1002, Folder 2)
    - 1976: Friedrich, Otto (Offsite-box 1002, Folder 3)
    - 1976: Gart, Murray (Offsite-box 1002, Folder 4)
    - 1976: Gordon, Leah (Offsite-box 1002, Folder 5)
    - 1976: Graves, Ralph (Offsite-box 1002, Folder 6)
    - 1976: Jamieson, Edward (Offsite-box 1002, Folder 7)
    - 1976: McManus, Jason (Offsite-box 1002, Folder 8)
    - 1976: Nickel, Herman (Offsite-box 1002, Folder 9)
    - 1976: Memos: A-Z (Offsite-box 1002, Folder 10-30)
    - 1976: Memos: A-Z [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1976: Staff Memos (Offsite-box 1002, Folder 31)
    - 1977: Ajemian, Bob (Offsite-box 1002, Folder 32)
    - 1977: Barrett, Larry (Offsite-box 1002, Folder 33)
    - 1977: Bernard, Walter (Offsite-box 1002, Folder 34)
    - 1977: Bernard, Walter [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1977: Birnbaum, Jesse (Offsite-box 1002, Folder 35)
    - 1977: Brack, Reginald (Offsite-box 1002, Folder 36)
    - 1977: Brine, Ruth (Offsite-box 1002, Folder 37)
    - 1977: Cave, Ray (Offsite-box 1003, Folder 1-2)
    - 1977: Church, George (Offsite-box 1003, Folder 3)
    - 1977: Church, George [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1977: Davidson, Ralph (Offsite-box 1003, Folder 4)
    - 1977: Donovan, Hedley (Offsite-box 1003, Folder 5-7)
    - 1977: Duffy, Martha (Offsite-box 1003, Folder 8)
    - 1977: Duncan, Dick (Offsite-box 1003, Folder 9)
    - 1977: Durniak, John (Offsite-box 1003, Folder 10)
    - 1977: Elson, John (Offsite-box 1003, Folder 11)
    - 1977: Ferenbaugh, Dorothy (Offsite-box 1003, Folder 12)
    - 1977: Foote, Timothy (Offsite-box 1003, Folder 13)
    - 1977: Friedrich, Otto (Offsite-box 1003, Folder 14)
    - 1977: Gart, Murray (Offsite-box 1003, Folder 15)
    - 1977: Gordon, Leah (Offsite-box 1003, Folder 16)
    - 1977: Graves, Ralph (Offsite-box 1003, Folder 17)
    - 1977: Heiskell, Andrew (Offsite-box 1003, Folder 18)
    - 1977: Jamieson, Edward (Offsite-box 1003, Folder 19)
    - 1977: Jaroff, Leon (Offsite-box 1003, Folder 20)
    - 1977: Kanfer, Steve (Offsite-box 1003, Folder 21)
    - 1977: Korn, Jerry (Offsite-box 1003, Folder 22)
    - 1977: Kriss, Ron (Offsite-box 1003, Folder 23)
    - 1977: Kunhardt, Phil (Offsite-box 1003, Folder 24)
    - 1977: Loeb, Marshall (Offsite-box 1003, Folder 25)
    - 1977: McManus, Jason (Offsite-box 1003, Folder 26)
    - 1977: Merrill, David (Offsite-box 1003, Folder 27)
    - 1977: Steed, Robert (Offsite-box 1003, Folder 28)
    - 1977: Sweeney, Bob (Offsite-box 1003, Folder 29)
    - 1977: Tinnin, Dave (Offsite-box 1003, Folder 30)
    - 1977: Wilson, Donald (Offsite-box 1003, Folder 31)
    - 1977: Zim, Marvin (Offsite-box 1003, Folder 32)
    - 1977: Memos from Merrick and Magnuson (Offsite-box 1003, Folder 33)
    - 1977: Staff Memos (Offsite-box 1003, Folder 34)
    - 1977: Notes from the Managing Editor (Offsite-box 1003, Folder 35)
    - 1977: Memos: A-H (Offsite-box 1003, Folder 36-42)
    - 1977: Memos: J-Z (Offsite-box 1004, Folder 1-13)
    - 1977: Memos: January-December (Offsite-box 1004, Folder 14-25)
    - 1977: Memos: January-December [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1978: Airey, Norm (Offsite-box 1004, Folder 26)
    - 1978: Bear, Charles (Offsite-box 1004, Folder 27)
    - 1978: Cave, Ray (Offsite-box 1004, Folder 28-31)
    - 1978: Clarke, Fred (Offsite-box 1004, Folder 32)
    - 1978: Davidson, Ralph (Offsite-box 1004, Folder 33)
    - 1978: Donovan, Hedley (Offsite-box 1004, Folder 34-35)
    - 1978: Duncan, Dick (Offsite-box 1004, Folder 36)
    - 1978: Duncan, Dick [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1978: Ferenbaugh, Dorothy (Offsite-box 1005, Folder 1)
    - 1978: Gart, Murray (Offsite-box 1005, Folder 2)
    - 1978: Gordon, Leah (Offsite-box 1005, Folder 3)
    - 1978: Graves, Ralph (Offsite-box 1005, Folder 4)
    - 1978: Heiskell, Andrew (Offsite-box 1005, Folder 5)
    - 1978: Jamieson, Edward (Offsite-box 1005, Folder 6)
    - 1978: Keylor, Arthur (Offsite-box 1005, Folder 7)
    - 1978: Korn, Jerry (Offsite-box 1005, Folder 8)
    - 1978: Kunhardt, Phil (Offsite-box 1005, Folder 9)
    - 1978: Lubar, Bob (Offsite-box 1005, Folder 10)
    - 1978: McManus, Jason (Offsite-box 1005, Folder 11)
    - 1978: Prendergast, Curt (Offsite-box 1005, Folder 12)
    - 1978: Rosen, Clare Mead (Offsite-box 1005, Folder 13)
    - 1978: Rosen, Clare Mead [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1978: Shepley, James (Offsite-box 1005, Folder 14)
    - 1978: Stolley, Richard (Offsite-box 1005, Folder 15)
    - 1978: Sutton, Kelso (Offsite-box 1005, Folder 16)
    - 1978: Sweeney, Bob (Offsite-box 1005, Folder 17)
    - 1978: Wilson, Donald (Offsite-box 1005, Folder 18)
    - 1978: Memos: A-Z (Offsite-box 1005, Folder 19-29)
    - 1978: Memos: A-Z [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1979: Banks, Louis (Offsite-box 1005, Folder 30)
    - 1979: Bear, Charles (Offsite-box 1005, Folder 31)
    - 1979: Brine, Ruth (Offsite-box 1005, Folder 32)
    - 1979: Brown, Dale (Offsite-box 1005, Folder 33)
    - 1979: Cave, Ray (Offsite-box 1005-1006)
    - 1979: Donovan, Hedley (Offsite-box 1006, Folder 5)
    - 1979: Duncan, Dick (Offsite-box 1006, Folder 6)
    - 1979: Gart, Murray (Offsite-box 1006, Folder 7)
    - 1979: Gordon, Leah (Offsite-box 1006, Folder 8)
    - 1979: Graves, Ralph (Offsite-box 1006, Folder 9-11)
    - 1979: Heiskell, Andrew (Offsite-box 1006, Folder 12)
    - 1979: Jamieson, Edward (Offsite-box 1006, Folder 13)
    - 1979: Korn, Jerry (Offsite-box 1006, Folder 14)
    - 1979: Kunhardt, Phil (Offsite-box 1006, Folder 15)
    - 1979: Lubar, Bob (Offsite-box 1006, Folder 16)
    - 1979: Manley, Joan (Offsite-box 1006, Folder 17)
    - 1979: McCandless, Carolyn (Offsite-box 1006, Folder 18)
    - 1979: McManus, Jason (Offsite-box 1006, Folder 19)
    - 1979: Prendergast, Curt (Offsite-box 1006, Folder 20)
    - 1979: Rogin, Gil (Offsite-box 1006, Folder 21)
    - 1979: Rosen, Clare Mead (Offsite-box 1006, Folder 22)
    - 1979: Rukeyser, Bill (Offsite-box 1006, Folder 23)
    - 1979: Shepley, James (Offsite-box 1006, Folder 24)
    - 1979: Stolley, Richard (Offsite-box 1006, Folder 25)
    - 1979: Wilson, Donald (Offsite-box 1006, Folder 26)
    - 1979: Memos: A-D (Offsite-box 1006, Folder 27-30)
    - 1979: Memos: E-W (Offsite-box 1007, Folder 1-11)
    - 1980: Ajemian, Bob (Offsite-box 1007, Folder 12)
    - 1980: Banks, Louis (Offsite-box 1007, Folder 13)